itulip.com 2008-06-22

# iTulip.com - Privacy Statement

iTulip, Inc. Privacy Statement  
   
PLEASE READ THIS PRIVACY STATEMENT CAREFULLY.  YOUR USE OF THIS WEBSITE OR ANY INFORMATION OR MATERIAL CONTAINED ON THIS SITE IS SUBJECT AT ALL TIMES TO THESE TERMS AND CONDITIONS. IF YOU DO NOT WISH TO BE BOUND BY THESE TERMS AND CONDITIONS, DO NOT ACCESS THIS SITE.  
   
Copyright © 2006 iTulip, Inc.  
ALL RIGHTS RESERVED  
   
iTulip.com is committed to safeguarding your privacy online. Please read the following statement to understand how your personal information will be treated as you make full use of the iTulip.com Web site. The iTulip.com Web site is owned and operated by iTulip, Inc.

If you have any questions regarding our privacy statement, please feel free to contact us by e-mail at info@itulip.com.  

Summary  
Our primary goal in collecting user information is to enhance your experience on our Web site.  We collect user name and email address data from users of our Forum as well as from subscribers to our Weekly Newsletter and Alerts email notices.  iTulip.com is committed to your privacy and will not share any personal information with any third party at any time, unless required by law.  
   
What this Privacy Policy Covers  
This privacy policy covers the Web site iTulip.com.   iTulip.com does not currently charge any fees to access iTulip.com web site content but reserves the right to charge a nominal fee for access to some content in the future.  Other iTulip.com sites linked to from this Web site, such as f4thcurrency.com, have their own privacy statements which can be viewed on those sites.

Please be aware that iTulip.com sponsors, advertisers, co-branded Web site or Web sites that have links on our site may collect personally identifiable information about you on their Web sites. The information practices of those parties are not covered by this privacy statement. iTulip.com users should also be aware that when you voluntarily disclose personal information in chat areas or bulletin boards, that information may be collected by others and may result in unsolicited messages from others.  

Security  
Your information is stored on iTulip.com Web servers hosted by Bluehost (http://www.bluehost.com) a Web hosting company based in the United States.  Bluehost uses various procedural and technical safeguards to protect information against loss or theft as well as unauthorized access and disclosure to protect information, including encryption, "firewalls" and Secure Socket Layers. Bluehost employs many different security techniques to protect such data from unauthorized access by users inside and outside the company. However, "perfect security" does not exist on the Internet.  
   
Privacy of Children  
Kids under 13: Do not send any information about yourself to us--including information such as your name, address, or e-mail address. We do not knowingly collect personally identifiable information from children under 13. In the event that we learn we have collected any personal information from a child under the age of 13 without verification of parental consent, we will delete that information from our database as quickly as possible.  The iTulip.com Forum uses the COPPA registration system. This complies with the COPPA laws and requires children under the age of 13 to get parental consent before they can post.  For more info about this law, see here: http://www.ftc.gov/bcp/conline/pubs/buspubs/coppa.htm  
   
As Required By Law  
iTulip.com may disclose your personal information if required to do so by law or in the good faith belief that such action is necessary to conform to the edicts of the law or comply with legal process served on iTulip.com or to protect and defend the rights or property of iTulip.com.  
   
Collecting of Information  

Voluntary Submission  

iTulip.com does not collect personally identifying information about any individual iTulip.com Web site user except when knowingly provided by such individual. For example, we may ask you for information, such as your e-mail address, zip code and the country in which you are viewing the Web site when you subscribe to the iTulip.com Forum or Newsletters, enter a contest or complete a survey. When you purchase items from the iTulip.com Gift Shop, you will be asked for additional personal information, such as your address, telephone number and credit card information, in order to complete the purchase. You always have the option not to provide the information we request.  
  
Cookies  
  
A cookie is a data file that certain Web sites write to your computer's hard drive when you visit such sites. A cookie file can contain information, such as a user identification code, that the site uses to track the pages you have visited. iTulip.com uses cookies to track user traffic patterns throughout the iTulip.com Web site and to remember your passwords and various preferences so that you don't have to reset them each time you visit the Web site. We use this data on an anonymous basis and we do not correlate this information with personal data of any user. Business partners of iTulip.com and vendors providing hosting and other services for iTulip.com., as well as advertisers who contract directly with a third-party service to serve their advertisements, may set their own cookies which may collect similar anonymous information.

Most Web site browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually change your browser settings to display a warning before accepting a cookie, or to refuse all cookies. However, if you choose to disable the receipt of cookies from our Web site, you may not be able to use certain features of the site.  
  
Browser Level Information  
  
iTulip.com Web servers (hosted by Bluehost) automatically collect information about a site user's IP address, browser type and the URL that you just came from (whether this URL is on the Web site or not) and which URL you next go to (whether this URL is on the Web site or not) by reading this information from the user's browser (information provided by every user's browser). This information is collected in a database and used--in an aggregated, anonymous manner--in our internal analysis of traffic patterns within our Web site. This information is automatically logged by most Web sites. iTulip.com also uses a SiteMeter.com javascript applet that runs in your browser when you are visiting the site if you have javascript enabled.  SiteMeter collects information similar to the information collected by our Web servers and is also used --  in an aggregated, anonymous manner--in our analysis of traffic patterns within our Web site. To block our collecting this data, simply disable javascript in your browser.  However, be aware that several functions of our Forum will not longer operate if you disable javascript.    
  
Use of Information  
  
To Target Content  
  
To develop content targeted to your interests, we use aggregated user information to determine which areas of our Web site users prefer based upon traffic to those areas. We do not track what individual users read, but instead how well each page or content area performs overall.  
  
To Provide Interactive Communications From iTulip.com  
  
To enhance your experience we may provide you with interactive communications, such as our electronic newsletters, to the e-mail address that you provide to us. Such interactive communications are provided only to those users who have expressly provided us with their permission to receive them as part of their user profile.

From time to time we may provide e-mails highlighting new features, promotions or contests on the Web site to those users who have expressly provided us with their permission to send such communications previously.  
  
To Provide Communications From Third Parties  
  
We respect the privacy of our users and shall not disclose or distribute our user list to any third party, nor shall it permit anyone else to do so.  
  
Control of Your Information  
  
Registered Forum users may change their Forum user profile by logging into the Forum and changing their profile in the Use CP (Control Panel)  to stop receiving email notifications, communications from other users, or any other source of communication by the site or other site users.  Newsletter subscribers can opt-out at any time or change the services previously requested.  
  
Sharing of Information  
  
When you are on an area of iTulip.com and are asked for personal information, you are sharing that information with iTulip.com as well as business partners and vendors providing hosting and other services for iTulip.com. If you do not want your information to be shared, you can choose not to allow the transfer of your information by not using that particular service. In addition, any personally identifiable information provided by our users as part of an advertiser promotion online may be provided directly to advertisers.  
  
Aggregate, Anonymous Information With Advertisers  
  
iTulip.com derives revenue from advertising.  Sharing information is essential in order to attract and retain advertisers.  We use the aggregated, anonymous information that we gather (as well as information from third-party market researchers) to describe our services to partners and to assist our advertisers and sponsors to better understand our audience. We do not disclose personally identifying information about our users to these parties.  
  
How to Contact Us  
If you have any questions regarding our privacy statement, please feel free to contact us by e-mail at info@itulip.com.  
Governing Law  
In the event of any dispute arising in connection with this website, such dispute will be governed and resolved in terms of the laws of the Commonwealth of Massachusetts and any party accessing this website agrees to submit to the jurisdiction of the United States of America.
